(Sheldon:)Oh, he didn't perform stand-up
comedy, he was a philosopher.
(Leonard:)You know, I think
were zeroing in on your problem.
(Sheldon:)Perhaps I'll spend some time
(Sheldon:)developing a unified
theory of comedy,
(Sheldon:)which will allow me to elicit
laughter from anyone at any time.
(Sheldon:)Unless they're German,
'cause that's a tough crowd.
(Leonard:)Are you set on people
laughing with you?
'Cause if you're cool with at you...
(Sheldon:)I don't get it.
(Bernadette:)Raj, when you said you
were gonna bring a date
(Bernadette:)to watch Penny's thing tonight,
I didn't think you meant Stuart.
(Howard:)Really? I never for a second
thought it'd be anything else.
(Raj:)I almost met someone last night,
but I blew it.
(Raj:)I was walking Cinnamon
and this girl introduced herself,